A Guide to the University of Virginia Faculty Senate, General Records of the Secretary, 1974-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia Faculty Senate General Records of the Secretary 1974-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-19/3/4.891
This collection consists of 3 boxes.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library.
Contents List
- Arora, Narinder S. 1982 (Box 1)
- Brown, Leonard 1979-1980 (Box 1)
- Bruck, Stephen 1979-1980 (Box 1)
- Gordon, Vivian and Hadden, Jeffrey 1984 (Box 1)
- Grave, Floyd K. 1980 (Box 1)
- Grieger, Ingrid 1982 (Box 1)
- Johnson, Heidi 1980-1982 (Box 1)
- Ms. Langman 1980 (Box 1)
- Murdaugh, J. Daniel (3 folders) 1982-1984 (Box 1)
- Paulsen 1983 (Box 2)
- Pietig, Jeanne 1984-1985 (Box 2)
- Procedures Manual 1976-1977 (Box 2)
- Reppucci, Christine 1980-1982 (Box 2)
- Ronell, Avital 1980 (Box 2)
- Scott, Leonard 1982-1983 (Box 2)
- Scouten, Alan 1982 (Box 2)
- Senate Committee on Faculty Relations 1974-1980 (Box 2)
- Uhl, Vincent W. (2 folders) 1977-1983 (Box 2)
- Wakat, Diane 1975-1980 (Box 3)
- Wiebenson, Dora 1979-1981 (Box 3)